/**
 * -------------------------------------------------------------------
 * Este archivo contiene todas las preguntas del examen
 * -------------------------------------------------------------------
 *  */ 

//temas de cada pregunta
const tema1 = 'Verb to be - Articles. Read and complete with the correct option:'
const tema2 = 'Verb to be - Negative and interrogative forms. Read and complete with the correct option:'
const tema3 = 'Question words. Read and complete with the correct option:'
const tema4 = 'Possessive pronouns. Read and complete with the correct option:'
const tema5 = 'Possessiveâ€™s. Read and complete with the correct option:'
const tema6 = 'Demonstrative pronouns. Read and complete with the correct option:'
const tema7 = 'Prepositions. Look at the pictures and answer the questions:'
const tema8 = 'Adjectives and adverbs. Read and complete correctly. (ex: loud = loudly):'
const tema9 = 'Intensifiers. Complete with the correct answer:'
const tema10 = 'Simple present. Complete with the correct answer:'
const tema11 = 'Simple present. Select affirmative, negative or interrogative sentences:'
const tema12 = 'Present tense. Complete with the correct answer:'




//preguntas
export const examenFinal = [
    //Preguntas del tema 1
    {
        pregunta: 'Pregunta de ejemplo, cualquier opcion es correcta.',
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} I _ _ English student.`,
        opciones: [
            'am, a',
            'am, an',
            'are, a',
            'are, an',
        ],
        respuesta: 'am, an',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} She _ _ Super Hero fan.`,
        opciones: [
            'am, a',
            'am, an',
            'is, a',
            'is, an',
        ],
        respuesta: 'is, a',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} _ you happy?`,
        opciones: [
            'Are',
            'Am',
            'Is',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Are',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} Green Lantern _ not a villain.`,
        opciones: [
            'am',
            'are',
            'is',
        ],
        respuesta: 'is',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} My father and I _ football fans."`,
        opciones: [
            'am',
            'are',
            'is',
        ],
        respuesta: 'are',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} _ Wonder Woman _ Amazon princess?`,
        opciones: [
            'is, a',
            'is, an',
            'are, a',
            'are, an',
        ],
        respuesta: 'is, an',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema1} Today _ _ fantastic day!`,
        opciones: [
            'is, a',
            'is, an',
            'are, a',
            'are, an',
        ],
        respuesta: 'is, a',
        img: '',
    },

    //Preguntas del tema 2
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} Wonder Woman _ a doctor, she _ a Super Hero.`,
        opciones: [
            'is not, are',
            'is not, is',
            'are not, are',
            'are not, is',
        ],
        respuesta: 'is not, is',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} _ you _ artist or a musician?`,
        opciones: [
            'Am, a',
            'Am, an',
            'Are, a',
            'Are, an',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Are, an',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} They _ friends, but they are nice.`,
        opciones: [
            'isn\'t',
            'aren\'t',
            'not',
        ],
        respuesta: 'aren\'t',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} It _ hot today, I am so happy!`,
        opciones: [
            'isn\'t',
            'aren\'t',
            'not',
        ],
        respuesta: 'isn\'t',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} I _ a zombie.`,
        opciones: [
            'am not',
            'are not',
            'is not',
        ],
        respuesta: 'am not',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} _ they wizards? No, they _.`,
        opciones: [
            'Am, isn\'t',
            'Am, aren\'t',
            'Are, isn\'t',
            'Are aren\'t',
            'Is, isn\'t',
            'Is, aren\'t',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Are, aren\'t',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema2} _ the Joker a Super Hero? No, he _.`,
        opciones: [
            'Are, isn\'t',
            'Are aren\'t',
            'Is, isn\'t',
            'Is, aren\'t',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Is, isn\'t',
        img: '',
    },

    //Preguntas del tema 3
    {
        pregunta: `${tema3} _ is Canada?`,
        opciones: [
            'Who',
            'Where',
            'When',
            'Why',
            'What',
            'How',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Where',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema3} _ is the interview.`,
        opciones: [
            'Who',
            'Where',
            'When',
            'Why',
            'What',
            'How',
        ],
        respuesta: 'When',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema3} _ is the new Math teacher?`,
        opciones: [
            'Who',
            'Where',
            'When',
            'Why',
            'What',
            'How',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Who',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema3} _ time is it?`,
        opciones: [
            'Who',
            'Where',
            'When',
            'Why',
            'What',
            'How',
        ],
        respuesta: 'What',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema3} _ is she from? She is from Italy.`,
        opciones: [
            'Who',
            'Where',
            'When',
            'Why',
            'What',
            'How',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Where',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema3} _ old are you? I am 12 years old.`,
        opciones: [
            'Who',
            'Where',
            'When',
            'Why',
            'What',
            'How',
        ],
        respuesta: 'How',
        img: '',
    },

    //Preguntas del tema 4
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} Batman is friend of Superman. Is _ friend.`,
        opciones: [
            'her',
            'his',
            'its',
        ],
        respuesta: 'his',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} _ name is Wonder Woman.`,
        opciones: [
            'His',
            'Its',
            'Her',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Her',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} The Flash and you are friends. He is _ friend.`,
        opciones: [
            'its',
            'your',
            'his',
        ],
        respuesta: 'your',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} This little house is for my dog. Is _ house.`,
        opciones: [
            'its',
            'his',
            'her',
        ],
        respuesta: 'its',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} We are humans, The Earth is _ planet.`,
        opciones: [
            'its',
            'our',
            'his',
        ],
        respuesta: 'our',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} My name is Lucy and she is _ mom. My mom's name is Anne.`,
        opciones: [
            'their',
            'my',
            'its',
        ],
        respuesta: 'my',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema4} They are Super Heroes, _ identity is a mistery.`,
        opciones: [
            'my',
            'our',
            'their',
        ],
        respuesta: 'their',
        img: '',
    },

    /* //Preguntas del tema 5
    {
        pregunta: `${tema5} My Super Hero _ suit.`,
        opciones: [
            's\'',
            '\'s',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema5} Their enemie _ powers.`,
        opciones: [
            's\'',
            '\'s',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema5} Your mother _ house.`,
        opciones: [
            's\'',
            '\'s',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    }, */

    //Preguntas del tema 6
    {
        pregunta: `${tema6} _ car is red and comfortable.`,
        opciones: [
            'This',
            'These',
        ],
        respuesta: 'This',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema6} _ flowers are beautiful.`,
        opciones: [
            'That',
            'Those',
        ],
        respuesta: 'That',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema6} Are _ books for me?`,
        opciones: [
            'this',
            'these',
        ],
        respuesta: 'these',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema6} Is _ you new house?`,
        opciones: [
            'that',
            'those',
        ],
        respuesta: 'that',
        img: '',
    },

    //Preguntas del tema 7
    {
        pregunta: `${tema7} Where is the apple?`,
        opciones: [
            'under',
            'on',
            'next to',
        ],
        respuesta: 'on',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema7} Where is the cat?`,
        opciones: [
            'between',
            'under',
            'in front of',
        ],
        respuesta: 'between',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema7} Where are my shoes?`,
        opciones: [
            'on',
            'next to',
            'under',
        ],
        respuesta: 'under',
        img: '',
    },

/*     //Preguntas del tema 8
    {
        pregunta: `${tema8} The tiger is _. It attacks _. (aggresive)`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema8} The Flash is a _ Super Hero. He runs _. (fast)`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema8} The students are _. They study the lesson _. (quiet)`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    }, */

    /* //Preguntas del tema 9
    {
        pregunta: `${tema9} Those horses are _ fast! (too/enough)`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema9} That's _ information, thank you. (enough/so)`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema9} My mom is a _ good singer. (very/enough)`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    }, */

    //Preguntas del tema 10
    {
        pregunta: `${tema10} We _ (like/likes) comics, they are fun!`,
        opciones: [
            'like',
            'likes',
        ],
        respuesta: 'like',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema10} Super Heroes _ (protect/protects) the planet.`,
        opciones: [
            'protect',
            'protects',
        ],
        respuesta: 'protect',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema10} Wonder Woman _ (help/helps) humans against evildoers.`,
        opciones: [
            'help',
            'helps',
        ],
        respuesta: 'helps',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema10} She _ (flight/flights) with her lasso of Truth.`,
        opciones: [
            'flight',
            'flights',
        ],
        respuesta: 'flights',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema10} They _ (need/needs) super powers to save humanity from Solomon Grundy and Gorilla Grodd.`,
        opciones: [
            'need',
            'needs',
        ],
        respuesta: 'needs',
        img: '',
    },

    //Preguntas del tema 11
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT NEGATIVE My friends read comic books.`,
        opciones: [
            'My friends don\'t read comic books.',
            'My friends desn\'t read comic books.',
        ],
        respuesta: 'My friends don\'t read comic books.',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT INTERROGATIVE My friends read comic books.`,
        opciones: [
            'Do my friends read comic books?',
            'Does my friends read comic books?',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Does my friends read comic books?',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT NEGATIVE She watches TV on weekends.`,
        opciones: [
            'She doesn\'t watches TV on weekends',
            'She doesn\'t watch TV on weekends',
            'She don\'t watches TV on weekends',
            'She don\'t watch TV on weekends',
        ],
        respuesta: 'She doesn\'t watch TV on weekends',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT INTERROGATIVE She watches TV on weekends.`,
        opciones: [
            'Does she watches TV on weekends?',
            'Does she watch TV on weekends?',
            'Do she watches TV on weekends?',
            'Do she watch TV on weekends?',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Does she watch TV on weekends?',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT AFFIRMATIVE Does my sister like French fries?`,
        opciones: [
            'My sister like French fries.',
            'My sister likes French fries.',
        ],
        respuesta: 'My sister likes French fries.',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT NEGATIVE Does my sister like French fries?`,
        opciones: [
            'My sister don\'t like French fries.',
            'My sister don\'t likes French fries.',
            'My sister doesn\'t like French fries.',
            'My sister doesn\'t likes French fries.',
        ],
        respuesta: 'My sister doesn\'t like French fries.',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT AFFIRMATIVE The boy doesn't jump the rope.`,
        opciones: [
            'The boy jump the rope.',
            'The boy jumps the rope.',
        ],
        respuesta: 'The boy jumps the rope.',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema11} SELECT INTERROGATIVE The boy doesn't jump the rope.`,
        opciones: [
            'Does the boy jump the rope?',
            'Does the boy jumps the rope?',
            'Do the boy jump the rope?',
            'Do the boy jumps the rope?',
        ],
        respuesta: 'Does the boy jump the rope?',
        img: '',
    },

    //Preguntas del tema 12
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12} Pauline and Bruce _ (work/works) at a bank.`,
        opciones: [
            'work',
            'works',
        ],
        respuesta: 'work',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12} They _ (is/are) siblings.`,
        opciones: [
            'is',
            'are',
        ],
        respuesta: 'are',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12} She _ (are/is) the manager and he _ (is/are) a clrek.`,
        opciones: [
            'are, is',
            'are, are',
            'is, are',
            'is, is',
        ],
        respuesta: 'is, is',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12} They _ (start/starts) work very early in the morning and _ (finish/finishes) work late in the afternoon.`,
        opciones: [
            'start, finish',
            'start, finishes',
            'starts, finish',
            'starts, finishes',
        ],
        respuesta: 'start, finish',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12} They _ (live/lives) close to the bank and their house _ (is/are) next to the park, so they _ (drive/drives) to work.`,
        opciones: [
            'live, is, drive',
            'live, is, drives',
            'live, are, drive',
            'live, are, drives',
            'lives, is, drive',
            'lives, is, drives',
            'lives, are, drive',
            'lives, are, drives',
        ],
        respuesta: 'live, is, drive',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12}`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12}`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: `${tema12}`,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
    {
        pregunta: ``,
        opciones: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            '',
        ],
        respuesta: '',
        img: '',
    },
]
